yeah um I'm sorry my mom's calling and I
don't know how to turn off the alerts
this has been my problem with technology
in the air age of quarantine know you've
humanized yourself this is I don't know
how to turn the alerts off on my
computer and she will likely call back
again so I'm sorry if that happened
hey guys welcome to stir-crazy the show
where you'll never know whether my
guests are actually wearing their pants
or not my guest today is the co-creator
in the star of every one with good
tastes favorite show shits Creek it's
dan levy hey good to see you ma'am I am
not wearing great pants right now if you
must know I put a sweater on to give the
illusion that I'm properly dressed but I
am still in sweatpants though it is a
comfortable conversation that we're
gonna have I thought it might help the
ease of our chat yeah yeah I want you
comfortable I want you ready exactly can
you can you set the scene for me a
little bit what room are you in
literally right now I'm in my office
right now where the magic happens where
the magic hopefully will happen yeah
it's you know it's a weird time it's a
very strive been cooking as has everyone
else on the internet apparently someone
sent me like an Instagram post of Kim
Kardashian making cream of wheat this
morning and I thought okay anything's
you know on the table at this point are
you taking care of yourself in the same
way you normally would be like are you
is it like who gives us I have worn this
hat for two weeks so I don't want to get
into hygiene right now but let's just
say this is the best we're gonna do and
it's not great you describe what's
underneath there what am I not a lot of
hair that is just growing in all
different directions and it's as a
collective it's not a great look it's a
it's like wiry Kramer hair and then
sides are really long it's like a
Sideshow Bob kind of effect right now
and I haven't had the the care I suppose
to really find the right products
because we're in a death spiral so the
same thing already in these days times
it's not not my priority right now my
priority is you know helping as best I
can and and making sure that we get
through this as a community maybe
maybe I guess I got flow bu could get
like the the self haircut thing did I
have often flirted with the idea of
shaving my head but the problem is I
don't have one of those heads that look
great like I'm not gonna look like a
sexy like marine when I get out of this
it's not that won't help anybody so all
we can really do is is throw a hat on
right now and and uh and focus on better
things to not not only have like anyone
with good comedic tastes discovered this
this show but also you've got your fair
share of some cool celebs have
discovered the show over the years no
less than everyone from Mariah Carey to
reportedly Jennifer Lawrence is a fan of
the show
hey dope I don't really know about the
Jennifer Lawrence thing someone must
have talked to her or she must have
mentioned it somewhere it's the first
I'm hearing about it I heard I think she
might have talked to Kathryn about it
I'd heard yeah I think that's what it
might have been have any friendships
blossomed from these new celebrity fans
of the show uh yeah and I seem to have
developed an online correspondence she
freed up some tickets to her Christmas
show this past December which was very
nice of her to do but we've never
actually met in person and part of me
feels like that's probably for the best
right I don't want to know what I would
do if I were to meet her and she
probably doesn't want to know what I
would do if I met her so a little bit of
social distancing at this point I think
is probably great I want to talk about
your the great characters you've created
on the show they're so indelible they're
gonna be in my mind forever I'm gonna
name one of your characters and you tell
me I'm forming your quarantine
[Applause]
I think Moira would probably be
strategizing ways of leaving the house
and bending the quarantine rules or
either that or she would be so hyper
quarantined that it would sort of give
everyone else anxiety I would also be
cleaning up likely a lot of her dishes I
don't think she's a woman who knows how
to do the dishes dear old dad Jonny is
he he seems like a voice of Jonny seems
like he would be a very pragmatic person
to have around I think he would probably
be of the entire family the most
reasonable and low-key right rose family
member to have during a quarantine yep
Alexis would be a nightmare I think just
constantly breaking quarantine and you'd
then have to ask her like who she saw
and today how long have they been
quarantined and you just basically be
infecting your home right and David I
kind of live within myself every day a
little bit so that's a nightmare one at
one one is enough you don't need to know
yeah one like particle of David living
inside me at all times is enough for a
lifetime as you look around your place
like have you learned in the last few
weeks like what's essential to you
Eirene ever hooked before I was gonna
have in the same situation I literally
have never cooked it's not good I
thought to myself if I you know I'm my
mind is quite pragmatic I like to think
that if I have this kind of isolation I
should probably come out of it with a
skill so I have been trying to cook on a
regular basis a couple days ago I made a
like a marinated salmon filet that
turned out looking like a kind of like a
chunk of cold that you would find in a
mine or something like it was not it was
pitch black uh-huh because I didn't have
the temperature down because I don't
cook and this is exactly my problem
I would rather pay for someone to cook
than to buy all the ingredients that go
into making something and then ruin it
and have to order a pizza anyway that
said all the things that I should
probably have
a long time ago I've been trying to
learn and home the salmon I made
yesterday was actually quite delicious
you lower heat tips for thought you
lower heat okay before I let you go 1-1
game if you'll indulge me we always we
play some charades down some hand stop
close wide hold hold
pull open open open door door open your
gymnast one of us is really bad at this
I'm bad no first word Hey oh how you
what was it then it was social
distancing was it great I don't know I
definitely I'm not going to the Olympics
for this that's for sure okay I was
doing distancing and then socializing
right I just looked like the grandmother
so expectations that that's my idea of
socializing let's see if I do any better
I won't okay great
stare staring eyes staring eyes looking
staring looking looking glancing glaring
belly drinking gluttony consumtion
consumption consumption glaring Glee
eyeballs seeing each other connecting
connections are we had a time Alan tell
me we're out of time I got action it was
that was hard
our producers really cruel it was binge
watching I was trying to do watch I'm
horrible I'm the worst so we just ended
this on like a complete note of failure
collectively and if this was an escape
room we would be locked inside we're
stuck in here forever together
it's a sad note to end on
but I do want to say congratulations
again on shits Creek here's my advice to
you though I want piece of advice
remember you're the next like it's your
the office cast you're the friends cast
over the next ten years
everybody's gonna ask you every single
day when the reunion is happening you
know that people are asking me now and
I'm like the show is not even off the
air yet but yeah I don't know what to
say I'm like weak if we just did a
reboot next year it would just be
another season of the show I don't even
know if we could call it a reboot yet we
need the dust to settle or and then I'll
see if an idea comes to me and we'll do
it maybe just put something on the
calendar say announce 10 years from the
state the reunions happening go for it
look for 2030 it's gonna be great it's
gonna be amazing
you're always great I hate that it had
to happen under these circumstances but
it's good to catch up with you man Stacy
they say and congrats on an amazing run
oceans thank you very much
[Music]
you